Guide to the Sala Udin Papers, 1980-2005 AIS.2006.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1995-2005; XIV.
  - Oak Hill reports, coordinating meeting agenda, and clippings, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    Beacon/Corcoran Jennison Partners, LLC Oak Hill Master Plan Update, February 2003.
    Bound meeting notes for Oak Hill, Phase II, 2003.
    Oak Hill HOPE VI Redevelopment Phase I report and update, March 4, 2003.
  - Palisades Park development Economic Impact Analysis, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Parkway Center Mall financing, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Pittsburgh Partnership for Neighborhood Development (PPND), 2004 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - PNC Park finances, meetings, and memoranda, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Projects Review report, August 12, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh Development Fund (PDF) correspondence, report, and Portfolio Analysis, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Real Estate Department, 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Resolution No. 50 authorizing a First Amendment to the Pittsburgh Development Fund Cooperation Agreement, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Schenley Heights Housing Initiative, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - South Side, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Troy Hill - Cowley Street Project, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Uptown Certified Redevelopment Area correspondence, meetings, reports, and other materials, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Uptown Development, February 19, 2004.
    Uptown Redevelopment Plan Financing Economic Development, Spring 2003, May 6, 2003.
    Uptown Redevelopment Plan Financing Economic Development, Spring 2003, May 14, 2003.
- Women and Minority Business Enterprises (W/MBE), 1982-2005; XV.
  The Women and Minority Business Enterprise (W/MBE) series is related to the Urban Redevelopment Authority series. The Urban Redevelopment Authority (URA) supports diversity in all Pittsburgh area business. They require "all projects in excess of $250,000 to submit a Minority and Women-Owned Business Enterprise Plan, which is analyzed both internally and by the City's M/WBE Review Commission, to ensure success in this area. The URA expects all contracts of this size to achieve or exceed the goal of awarding 18% of the total project costs to MBE's and 7% of total project costs to WBE's."
  The M/WBE series contains a history of the Minority/Women's Business Enterprise development program, participation plans and performance audits, correspondence to and from a variety of Pittsburgh area business, organizations, and individuals, conference materials, contract and plan review summaries, meeting memoranda, proposals, policies, and committee materials, and news coverage. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - A & A Consultants, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action Conference proposal for M/WBE, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - African American Chamber of Commerce, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny County Minority Business Enterprise Participation Plan, 1982, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Allegheny AFL-CIO, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The Allegheny Group, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Aliya Contracting Construction Management, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Authority Resolutions 80 and 121 of 1994; 18 of 1995; and Ordinance 51, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - B.E.A.R. - Kennard Field Bleachers, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Black Contractor's Association (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Governmental Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Committees - Oversight Committee, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Review Committee City Code, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Review Committee meetings and memoranda, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Statewide Task Force, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Contract policy, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Contract review summary, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Cultural District Service Center, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - The Delta Organization, March 27, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Don Todd Associates, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Ebony Development, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - FLT Trading, Inc., 2003 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - High Tower, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Hill House Association, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - House Bill No. 1563, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - MJ Financial Answers, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Mayor's Committee of Business and Employment appointments, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Minority Enterprise Corporation - Power Conference 2000, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - The Mony Group, Inc., 2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - News coverage of W/MBEs, 2001, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Occasions of a Lifetime (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Ordinance for M/WBEs in Baltimore, MD, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Participation Plan for Three Rivers Demolition (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Partners for Livable Communities, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Pillar Awards, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Predatory businesses (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Proposal for Alliance for Development of Construction Contractors draft, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Proposed Unified Certification for Disadvantaged Business Enterprises (DBE), 2000-2005 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Quik-It Chicken, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Reports - Office of Business and Employment Opportunities - City of Pittsburgh MBE/WBE Planned Review Summary, FY 2000 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Reports - Contract Management Services (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Reports - Correcting Current Problems with M/WBE Contracting Programs in the Pittsburgh Region and Pennsylvania, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Reports - Housing Authority MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Reports - Maryland Department of Transportation - Utilization of MBE by the State of Maryland, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Reports - Minority and Women Business Development Program City of Pittsburgh, PA History, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Reports - Minority and Women Business Enterprise Program Performance Audit, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Reports - Minority and Women Business Enterprise Utilization Affirmative Action Requirements (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Reports - Parking Authority MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Reports - Sports and Exhibition Authority reports (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Construction Management Services MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000, 1.
    - Convention Center Construction MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000, 2.
    - North Shore Infrastructure MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000, 3.
    - PNC Park Baseball Stadium Construction Home of the Pittsburgh Pirates MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000, 4.
  - Reports - Sports and Exhibition Authority Pittsburgh Steeler's Stadium Construction MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Reports - URA Reports MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reports - Water and Sewer Authority MBE/WBE Contract Review Summary, FY 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reorganization, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Resource Center, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Rycon Construction - M/WBE Enterprise Plan, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - SGS Group, LLC, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Shults Ford, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Small Seeds Development, Inc., 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Soffer Office Building M/WBE plan, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sterling Contracting, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Value Added Foods, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - W & W Demolition, Exc., 1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Women's Enterprise Center (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Audio/Visual Media, 1996-2004; XVI.
  The Audio/Visual Media series contains audiocassette tapes and VHS tapes related to legislative meetings, committee meetings, budget meetings, task force activities, public hearings, news segments, informational videos, and other public relations materials. The cassettes within the series include both sound and visual recordings of Sala Udin.
  - Audio Cassettes, 1.
    The Audio Cassettes subseries is comprised of cassette tapes of sound recordings.
    - Post Agenda Civilian Review copy 1, October 16, 1996; 1. (Box 25)
    - Post Agenda Civilian Review copy 2, October 16, 1996; 2.
    - Sala Udin WYEP Black History Month, February 1999; 3.
    - Wessel Meet with Attorneys, November 13, 1997; 4.
    - Two (2) unlabeled tapes, 5.
  - VHS Cassettes, 2.
    The VHS Cassettes subseries is comprised of Video Home System tapes of visual recordings. Subjects include: committee meetings, NAACP, planning and development, public hearings, and transporatation.
    - Public Hearing, February 11 and 25, 1999; 1. (Box 25)
    - Standing Committee meeting, March 3, 1999; 2.
    - Standing committee meeting, May 20, 1999; 3.
    - Legislative Meeting and Standing committee Meeting, October 12-13, 1999; 4.
    - Standing Committee meeting part 2, October 13, 1999; 5.
    - Legislative Meeting, May 25, 1999; 6.
    - Budget Hearing, November 22-24, 2004; 7.
      The Audio/Visual Media Series contains audiocassettes and VHS cassettes of committee meetings, budget hearings, legislative meetings, informational videos, news segments, conference proceedings, and task force meetings.
    - "Miracle Church", 8.
    - Zone Based Advocacy TRT, 9.
    - MARC Public Relations Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership Gridlock, June 21, 2002; 10.
    - Are You OK? Informational Video, 11.
    - NAACP HIV/AIDS Film Project, 12.
    - PA High-Speed Maglev Project, February 2002; 13.
    - House on Fire NAACP & DuPont Pharm. HIV/AIDS Video Outreach Project, 14.
    - Coming to Life NAACP & DuPont Pharm. HIV/AIDS Video Outreach Project, 15.
    - Sister's Keeper NAACP & DuPont Pharm. HIV/AIDS Video Outreach Project, 16.
    - Don't Gridlock Event News, June 26, 2002; 17.
    - WPXI Sala Udin on Impact, 18.
    - Police, Engineering and Construction, Public Works, Parks; Public Safety, Municipal Investigation Fire Ems; Mayor's Office EORC, 2004; 19.
    - City of Pittsburgh Downtown Planning Collaborative Conference, March 3-4, 2000; 20.
    - City of Pittsburgh Post Agenda "Pittsburgh Works", April 8, 1999; 21.
    - Riverlife Task Force Three Rivers Park, 22.
    - Three (3) unlabeled VHS cassettes, 23